[Music]
[音乐]
all right you ready to do this yes sir
好的，你准备好了吗，先生
all right all right can you hang on
好吧好吧你能坚持下去吗
oh yeah just uh okay first things first
哦，是的，首先，首先
we don't have a lot of time as always so
我们没有那么多时间
you know find us in the Twitter we're
你知道在Twitter上找到我们
here after this I'm doing a book signing
在这里之后，我正在做书签名
I think at the pivotal booth for my my
我想在我的关键展位
last book but I've got a new book coming
最后一本书，但是我有一本新书
so that's confusing and the code is all
所以这很混乱，代码就是全部
there and that in that get repository so
在那里，在那个获取仓库中
you know find the lights just come back
你知道发现灯光刚回来
on I like it when is there you go turn
我喜欢它，当你走到那儿时
it off you know let it out a little bit
把它关掉，你知道让它出来一点
just relax get the music on I'm a de
放松一下，让音乐成为我
sangría o clock alright so um yeah hi
sangríao clock好吧，嗯，嗯，嗨
buddy hey how's it going
哥们你好吗
oh good great sang from Google yep whoa
哦，是来自Google的好歌手，哇！
yeah and happy to be doing this all
是的，很高兴做这一切
together yeah Google we know for google
一起耶Google我们知道Google
cloud we'll have many many services that
云，我们将有很多服务
you can use that it's probably all most
您可以使用它可能是大多数
of you needs but you know one of the
您的需求，但您知道其中之一
things I tried to do was to trying to
我试图做的是
make some of these services a lot easier
使其中一些服务更容易
to use and so I Google Google cloud we
使用，所以我谷歌谷歌云我们
started this new project called spring
开始了这个名为spring的新项目
cloud GCP it's been going on for about a
云GCP，它已经持续了大约
year and a half now I think yeah it's
一年半现在我想是的
been fun too it's been awesome and we
太有趣了，这太棒了，我们
are working with the pivotal engineers
正在与关键工程师合作
as well to make some of these really
以及使其中一些真正
nice intuitions and this is just what
很好的直觉，这就是
he's saying and this is important there
他在说，这很重要
are people at Google who are paid full
是Google的全薪员工
time to work on things to make Springs
是时候做一些让Springs成长的事情了
lives easier spring developers lives
生活更轻松Spring开发人员的生活
easier right yes so there's a people
比较容易，是的，所以有一个人
task for this it's not just as much as
为此的任务不只是
we'd like to be able to follow along as
我们希望能够跟随
fast as Google is going we don't have to
像Google一样快，我们不必
right there it's just being taken care
就在那里，只是被照顾
of for us by the team so that's awesome
团队为我们准备的
yeah what somebody is a sending me a
是的，有人向我发送了
message and I think that's kind of silly
信息，我认为这很愚蠢
all right so good stuff um so we're
好吧，好东西，嗯，我们
gonna talk about Google Cloud yeah right
要谈谈Google Cloud是的
where do you uh I I think it's worth
你在哪里，我认为这值得
maybe logging into Google cloud is that
也许登录到Google云是
fair sure yeah so how many people here
可以肯定的是，这里有多少人
people here are using cool Google Cloud
这里的人正在使用很棒的Google Cloud
oh I use the Google file before who's
哦，我先使用Google文件
heard of it well Google there you go
听说得很好Google在那里
yeah
是的
not bad about yeah so for poppin we have
对，不错，所以对于poppin
a lot of different things like we got
很多不同的东西，比如我们
the basics at virtual machines and if
虚拟机的基础知识以及
you are into containers in communities
您正在社区中的容器中
you can run that as well
你也可以运行
that's all managed for you and we have
这一切都为您管理，我们有
services from machine learning to Big
从机器学习到大型服务
Data so you don't have to really
数据，因此您不必真正
maintain any of the infrastructure and
维护任何基础架构并
that's really the goal in the cloud
这才是云计算的目标
right you can bring and run your own
对，你可以带上自己的东西
environments but at the end of days
环境，但最终
probably really nice if you don't have
如果没有的话可能真的很好
to manage your infrastructure and being
管理您的基础架构
able to just use the services that we
能够使用我们提供的服务
provide
提供
right and what an infrastructure that's
正确的基础设施
a good point
好点
did you said there's a steam thing going
你说有事要发生吗
on there yeah that's interesting I hope
是的，我希望这很有趣
you can see that I'm not the only one
你可以看到我不是唯一的一个
seeing that right it's not fired that's
看到正确的，它不会被解雇的是
like so it's infrastructure is a great
就像这样，它的基础设施很棒
point right we want to be able to run
正确点，我们希望能够运行
applications Google cloud is great at
Google Cloud擅长的应用程序
running Cloud Foundry it's great at
运行Cloud Foundry非常擅长
running kubernetes I can run
运行我可以运行的kubernetes
applications like standard stock
像标准库存这样的应用
standard Springwood applications a
标准Springwood应用程序a
number of different ways there without a
没有的多种不同方式
pane and so then once that's out of the
窗格，所以一旦离开
way what can I focus on well I can focus
我可以专注于什么方式
on the things that that mean you know
在那意味着你知道的事情上
the things that I want in my application
我在应用程序中想要的东西
the things that support what I'm trying
支持我正在尝试的东西
to do in my software right services
在我的软件权利服务中做
infrastructure operations these kinds of
这些基础设施运营
things that are just tedious to manage
繁琐的事情
myself the lifecycle of which I don't
我自己的生命周期
want to think about so to have Google
想这样想拥有Google
cloud do that is interesting and I think
云做到这一点很有趣，我认为
today we're going to talk about a number
今天我们要谈一个数字
of different things we're gonna go from
我们将要去的不同事物
some things that you could do in a
您可以在
regular sort of non Google cloud place
非Google云端场所的常规类型
right you would in theory if you wanted
对，如果您愿意，理论上您会的
to if that was your inclination um but
如果那是你的倾向，但
it's just easier to let let big G manage
让大G管理起来更容易
it for you right sure
它肯定适合你
um and then we're gonna we're gonna move
嗯然后我们要去
to to some things that are unique I
一些独特的东西
think to to Google cloud we're just
想到Google Cloud，我们只是
gonna talk about some of the things
要谈论一些事情
where it's clear that somebody has
很明显有人在
thought about this stuff it's stuff that
想到这个东西
you could probably approximate with a
你可能会估计一个
lot of really just way too much extra
真的太多了
work right it's just nice to not have to
正确地工作，不用去也很好
worry about it and then there's some
担心它，然后有一些
things that you definitely can't do
你绝对做不到的事情
anywhere else and I think one of the
在其他任何地方，我认为其中之一
things I hope that you will see is
我希望你会看到的是
through some of these integrations
通过其中一些集成
especially through the abstraction that
特别是通过抽象
spring gives you you're not really tied
春天给你带来的束缚
to the Google cloud services at all
完全使用Google云服务
because through some of these generic
因为通过这些通用
abstractions you're writing spring code
您正在编写Spring代码的抽象
and you can run the same
你可以运行相同的
code on Google cloud were in another
Google云上的代码位于另一个
services well if you need to switch any
服务很好，如果您需要切换任何
of the backends you can without having
您无需拥有的后端
to change all of the code base so spring
改变所有的代码库
gives you portability here but it also
在这里为您提供可移植性，但同时
doesn't deprive you of the the if you
如果您不剥夺您的
want to you know if you want to like use
想知道您是否想使用
these api's to their fullest that's
这些api是最大的
there as well and we're not trying to
那里，我们也不想
hide power from you okay so first things
隐藏力量，好吧，第一件事
first let's start by building an
首先让我们建立一个
application we're gonna build the
我们将要构建的应用程序
Springwood application and I want to I'm
Springwood应用程序，我想
gonna do so I'm gonna you know the first
我会做的，你会知道第一个
thing I wanna do is I wanna build an
我想做的是建立一个
application that talks to a sequel
与续集对话的应用程序
database yeah I've got Google cloud
数据库，是的，我有Google Cloud
platform here I I happen to have a nice
我这里的平台碰巧有一个不错的
account with all sorts of actually price
各种实际价格的帐户
if price is an issue Google pretty
如果价格是一个问题，谷歌漂亮
routinely comes in Cheaper for a lot of
通常会便宜很多
things but that's besides the point I
事情，但那不是我要说的
happen to have unlimited spend so I like
碰巧有无限的支出，所以我喜欢
to I like to just create things and see
我喜欢创造事物并看到
what happens and see who sends me a
会发生什么，看看谁给我发了
notification from pivotal saying hey so
关键的通知说嘿
what we're gonna do is we're gonna
我们要做的是
create an application that talks to
创建一个与之对话的应用程序
let's just start with something simple
让我们从简单的事情开始
and familiar database like a sequel
和熟悉的数据库，例如续集
server write my sequel my sequel
服务器写我的续集我的续集
something like that and so you go to the
这样的事情，所以你去
Google cloud platform you can create an
您可以创建Google云平台
account can they create a free account
他们可以创建一个免费帐户
or anything like that or yeah you can't
或类似的东西，是的，你不能
actually create a account right now and
实际上现在创建一个帐户
tell you get free credit so I think it's
告诉您获得免费信用，所以我认为
three hundred dollar credit if you are
三百美元的信贷，如果你是
able to write you $300 yeah yeah well I
可以给你写300美元是的，我很好
I'm not saying that there's a
我并不是说有一个
competition or anything going on here
竞争或发生的任何事情
but I didn't talk about his er this
但我没有谈论他的这个
morning although he had two hundred
早上虽然他有两百
bucks
雄鹿
oh really yeah well then that's good to
哦，是的，那很好
know about I never had to sign off
知道我从来不需要退出
without be maybe there's two hundred
也许没有两百
euros either way either way it sounds
欧元要么听起来
like a bigger might I'm an American so
像一个更大的人，我可能是美国人
my math isn't great but three hundred as
我的数学不好，但三百
far as I know is bigger than two hundred
据我所知大于200
so I'm gonna create a sequel data store
所以我要创建一个续集数据存储
I'm gonna go to sequel and you've got
我要去续集，你有
some good options here create an
这里有一些不错的选择
instance if I wanted to I'm not gonna do
实例，如果我想我不会做
it we've got two very very venerable
它有两个非常非常古老的
options how many of you using one or
选择多少人使用一个或
either of these one or both of these
这些之一或全部
things my sequel or PostgreSQL good
我的续集或PostgreSQL好东西
stuff oh yeah yeah okay so very much you
东西哦，是的，好的，非常你
know I think a plurality at least from
我至少至少知道
I've got an instance
我有一个实例
this actually to my chagrin and my
这实际上令我cha恼，
embarrassment you're gonna see us work
尴尬，你会看到我们的工作
with and and interact with things that
与和与之互动
are globally distributed later on not
后来分布在全球
this this isn't it right now and those
这不是现在，那些
things take no time at all to spin up
事情根本不需要时间来加速
but for some reason this takes minutes
但由于某种原因，这需要几分钟
like an actual solid lifetime minutes of
就像是
your life you know so I'm not gonna spin
你的生活你知道，所以我不会旋转
up a new instance live even though I
建立一个新实例，即使我
could and so I've got an instance of
可以，所以我有一个实例
this database here on my local machine
我本地计算机上的此数据库
behind the scenes here reservations my
在幕后这里保留我的
sequel that DB or my sequel DB also you
续集那个DB或我的续集DB也是你
notice that I've got this shell down
注意我已经把这个壳放下来了
here right I like the shell it's a show
在这里，我喜欢贝壳，这是一个表演
based in the browser
基于浏览器
it's a browser shell it's a bell it's
这是一个浏览器外壳，这是一个钟声
coded I'll show cloud shell yeah hands
编码，我将向您展示云壳
so it's a cloud browser shell and and
所以它是一个云浏览器外壳，并且
the point is I'm logged into an account
关键是我已登录帐户
that's already got all of the G cloud
已经拥有了所有的G云
tools set up so I can actually you know
设置工具，以便我实际上您可以知道
if I wanted to interact with the API I
如果我想与API交互，
could do G cloud and then what let's do
可以做G云，然后我们要做
us what do we do a sequel connect sequel
我们我们该怎么做续集连接续集
Connect okay and then you can connect to
连接好，然后您可以连接到
the sequel instance so you just create
续集实例，因此您只需创建
it yeah one like that exactly that'll
是的，就像那样
take a few minutes you know background
花几分钟你知道背景
there right but it's gonna actually log
那里正确，但实际上会记录
me into my account so if I wanted to
我进入我的帐户，所以如果我想
administer my database I could do that
管理我的数据库，我可以做到这一点
that's just interesting that you have
有趣的是
that there so if you're not sure about
在那里，所以如果您不确定
something and you really want to do it
有些事情，你真的想做
you can you can do that instance is
你可以做那个实例是
being updated yeah so what happened
是的，所以发生了什么事
behind the scenes is that when you spin
幕后花絮是，当您旋转时
up as my sequel or Postgres sequel
作为我的续集或Postgres续集
obviously don't want this to be on
显然不希望这样
public Internet or a lot of anybody can
公共互联网或许多人都可以
get access to it so what happens behind
得到它，所以后面会发生什么
the scenes and is that we will follow
场景，就是我们将跟随
what this off so when you use the G call
这怎么办，当您使用G通话时
come in line behind the scene to connect
排在幕后排成一列
with the sequel instance we will
与续集实例，我们将
actually configure and we open up a
实际配置，我们打开一个
connection for you securely and to do
安全地为您建立联系
that that's why we need to kind of add
这就是为什么我们需要添加
like IP address temporarily but then we
暂时喜欢IP地址，但随后我们
do these things transparently from the G
从G透明地做这些事情
cloud coming online for you so you don't
云为您上线，因此您不会
have to deal with it right and now
现在必须要处理
you're logged in you do have a database
您已经登录，您确实有一个数据库
that's good yeah so I've got a database
很好，所以我有一个数据库
called reservations I'm already we've
叫做预订，我已经是我们了
created this up front I'm gonna say
我先说了这个
describe the table called reservations
描述称为保留的表格
there you go it's got an ID
你去那里有一个ID
field and a name field it's all managed
字段和名称字段全部托管
trimming by the cloud good stuff now I
现在我被云整理好了
want to connect to this from my
想要从我这里连接
application yeah and so I've got an
是的，所以我有一个
instance connection name and I'm gonna
实例连接名称，我要
use that when I create my spring mood
当我创造春天的心情时用它
application so let's go back to start
应用程序，让我们回到开始
that spring that I hope we're gonna
那年春天，我希望我们会
create a new application call this GCP
创建一个名为GCP的新应用
I'm imaginative like that I'm gonna use
我很有想像力
the GCP support I'm gonna use GCP
我要使用GCP的GCP支持
messaging and GCP storage okay okay
消息传递和GCP存储好吧好吧
Lombok web we want JDBC and we're using
Lombok网站，我们需要JDBC，我们正在使用
my sequel right so I'm gonna bring in
我的续集对，所以我要引进
the my sequel dependency as well and I
我对续集的依赖
think that's enough for now now GCP
认为现在GCP就足够了
support is actually gonna activate them
支持实际上会激活他们
the Bill of Materials maven bomb so even
物料清单Maven炸弹甚至
though there's a good deal many more and
虽然还有很多很多
I mean a good deal many more like just a
我的意思是很多很多像
crazy you would you'll be up all week
疯了，你会整周都起来
just trying to remember it's not it'll
只是想记住那不是
never end you'll find that there are
永无止境，你会发现有
more dependencies for Google then there
对Google的依赖程度更高
are sands in the universe grains of sand
是宇宙中的沙子沙粒
in the universe but that said there's a
在宇宙中，但是那有一个
good deal many more than we have
比我们拥有的要多得多
supported here on the initializer that's
在初始化器的支持
okay you just need to know their their
好吧，你只需要知道他们的
artefact ID and then the goop ID is
人工制品ID，然后，树冠ID为
usually the same and and the version you
通常和您所使用的版本相同
don't have to worry about it because
不必担心，因为
it's managed by the Bill of Materials
由物料清单管理
dependency that brings that gets brought
带来的依赖
in from GCP support right there yeah
来自GCP支持
okay hit go and we're going to build an
好吧，去吧，我们将建立一个
application that talks to the the sequel
与续集对话的应用程序
data store that we just talked about
我们刚才讨论的数据存储
right yeah okay so LS la okay CD
是的，好的，所以LS la好的CD
downloads okay you what's that
下载好了，那是什么
excuse me Oh awkward that was so last
对不起，那太残酷了
hour a totally different talk I've moved
一个小时，我已经彻底改变了谈话
on okay so here we go start that up
好的，现在我们开始
there we go
我们去
okay it's already written oh that's
好吧，它已经写了哦，那是
Kafka that's gonna say that was yeah
Kafka那会说是的
you're really good raaah wrong
你真的很好啊
application right there yeah all right
那里的应用程序是的，没事
but I think ours is quite empty right
但我认为我们的是空的
now right probably nothing anyone hopes
现在可能没有人希望
I mean yes you did you did that spring
我的意思是你那年春天做了
food two point one point five right yeah
食物2点1点5对
yeah very good yeah okay awesome there
是的，很好，那里很棒
it is so we're using the latest and
因此，我们正在使用最新的
greatest spring book JDBC would start
最伟大的 spring book JDBC将会开始
aware of a starter pub/sub storage the
知道初学者发布/订阅存储
key bit here is the supreme kai
这里的关键是至上
dependencies yep so we're actually part
是的，所以我们实际上是一部分
of the spring coalition so that's why
春季联盟的原因，这就是为什么
over here in the dependency in the
在这里的依赖中
bureau material you just have to include
您只需包括的局材料
spring cloud-like which release and you
春天的云状释放，你
get all of the dependencies version
获取所有依赖项版本
managed for you of course you don't
为您管理当然不是
include the dependency unless if you
包括依赖项，除非您
explicitly declare it so for example for
明确声明它，例如
cloud sequel you do need to include the
云续集，您需要包括
cloud sequel dependency right yeah now
云续集依赖现在是的
of course you can connect your class
当然你可以联系你的班级
sequel by GBC driver directly but that
由GBC驱动程序直接续作，但是
may require you to open up some ports so
可能需要您打开一些端口，所以
if you want to have internal private IP
如果您想拥有内部专用IP
axis which you can then you just use
您可以使用的轴
your regular JDBC driver however if you
您的常规JDBC驱动程序，但是如果您
want to connect it from the outside or
想要从外部连接它，或者
the you know securely from another cloud
您可以从另一个云安全地知道
or just from your laptop then you can
或只是从笔记本电脑上，您就可以
use our starter which is the cloud
使用我们的启动器，即云
support starter by doing that we will
通过这样做来支持初学者
actually authenticate yourself your
真正验证您的身份
application against Google Cloud and
针对Google Cloud的应用程序和
establish your secure tunnel which then
建立您的安全隧道，然后
you can connect to our database without
您可以连接到我们的数据库而无需
having to go to the regular public axis
不得不去常规的公共轴线
okay okay so what I got the database
好吧好吧，所以我得到了数据库
name you need this bring that data
名字你需要这个带那个数据
source that URL you need actually you
实际获取您需要的URL
need the GCP sequel instance me and
需要我的GCP续集实例，
that's what this connection Ian so if
这就是伊恩的联系，如果
you scroll down to the council you need
您向下滚动到所需的理事会
this entire string that uniquely
这整个字符串唯一
identifies this database instance and
标识此数据库实例，并
then I need the password yes you do need
那我需要密码是的
your usually and password now typically
您通常的密码和现在的密码
there's no password but Josh I think we
没有密码，但乔希，我想我们
set one for you yep
为你设置一个
so it's secure yeah exactly yeah
所以它是安全的，是的，是的
your password is totally secure secure
您的密码是完全安全的
right now okay yeah nobody sees nobody
现在好吧，是的，没人看到
but your database name is a little
但是你的数据库名有点
correct so if we go back there you need
正确，所以如果我们回到那里，您需要
to add I think what database name is
添加我认为数据库名称是什么
actually reservations it's alright so if
实际上保留它没关系，所以如果
you go through database right there okay
你就在那里浏览数据库好吗
yeah and I think you were doing some
是的，我想你正在做一些
reservations okay so as you can see here
保留好，所以你可以在这里看到
even though we have some Google Cloud
即使我们有一些Google Cloud
specific attributes you can also use
您还可以使用特定的属性
spring data source to configure
spring数据源配置
everything else like connection pooling
其他一切，如连接池
username password and stuff like that
用户名密码和类似的东西
okay okay so we're gonna create a beans
好的，好的，我们要创建一个beans
gonna be in an application ready event
即将参加应用准备活动
it's gonna listen for that event my
我要去听那个事件
sequel and of course in order to talk to
续集，当然是为了和
that datastore I'm gonna use a venerable
我要使用的那个数据存储
JDBC template from days of yore and I
我和以前的JDBC模板
can add a constructor or I can just use
可以添加一个构造函数，或者我可以只使用
Lombok and use the required args
龙目岛并使用所需的参数
constructor and all I want to do is I
构造函数，我要做的就是
want to say call this database and query
想说调用此数据库并查询
for it so select all from reservation
为此，请从预订中全选
tables yep the reservation I don't all
桌子是保留我不是全部
figured out a new row mapper and the row
找出一个新的行映射器和行
mapper is gonna map data into a type of
映射器将数据映射到一种
static class reservation
静态班级预订
okay I'll private integer maybe yeah ie
好吧，我将私有整数也许是的，即
and private string name and I'm gonna
和私人字符串名称，我要
say at data at all hours constructor at
随时在数据上说构造函数
nor its constructor I'm gonna visit each
也不是我要去的建设者
one of those returned new reservation
其中之一返回了新​​的预订
nope not quite and type it already new
不完全不是，请输入新的
reservation and it's gonna be our result
保留，这将是我们的结果
set that get integer ID and result set
设置获取整数ID和结果集
that get string name okay and that just
可以得到字符串名称，
returns a lambda good stuff okay so I'm
返回好东西的lambda好吧，所以我
now I'm gonna visit each one of those
现在我要去拜访那些
I'll say query that for each and I'll
我会说查询每个，然后
just log it out and I'll do that with a
只需注销即可，我将通过
logger that I'm gonna synthesized using
我将使用合成的记录器
Lombok Oh ready good
龙目岛哦准备好了
now did you add the the starter into
现在您是否将启动器添加到
your pump Axum oh I think it did
你的泵阿克苏姆，哦，我想
oh nice nice yeah very good so let's run
哦，很好，很好，很好，让我们开始吧
that and see what we get
那，看看我们得到什么
good stuff I see so what's gonna happen
我看到好东西，那会发生什么
next is that in the log over here if
接下来是在这里登录
everything work out fine let me see if I
一切正常，让我看看是否
can zoom in right here you can see that
可以在这里放大，您可以看到
just by adding the dependency and also
只需添加依赖项
some of the Google Cloud specific
一些特定于Google Cloud的内容
configuration we're actually obtaining
我们实际获得的配置
an ephemeral certificate that can then
临时证书，然后
snap into a secure connection into your
快速连接到您的安全连接中
database right so this is done
数据库正确，这样就完成了
automatically behind the scenes for you
自动为您幕后
which is pretty cool in the reason that
这很酷，因为
this is authenticated is because of the
这是经过验证的，因为
G cloud come in line that Josh has
乔希（Josh）
already installed and that is already
已经安装并且已经
authenticated with his username so that
使用他的用户名进行身份验证，以便
we can establish this authentication as
我们可以建立此身份验证为
well right yeah if you don't want to use
好吧，是的，如果您不想使用
three o'clock coming online if you're
如果您三点钟上线
running this on the server then you can
然后在服务器上运行它
download what we call a service account
下载我们所谓的服务帐户
which is a credential file that you can
这是一个凭证文件，您可以
put in you know securely somewhere on
安全地放在你知道的地方
your data path and you can set the
您的数据路径，您可以设置
environment variable 2.28 instead okay
环境变量2.28相反，可以
cool so do not work did it connect what
酷，所以不工作，它连接什么
13 connected oh that's many many
13个连接哦，很多很多
connections right there Wow
那里的连接哇
yeah I think you should probably limit
是的，我认为您应该限制
the connection for a little bit so poor
连接有点差
yeah so if you go to your application
是的，所以如果你去申请
yeah it's cody max max yep
是的，这是Cody Max Max Yeep
max I said it too - yeah okay where
我也说过了-是的，好的
exactly oh I don't see well you have
哦，我不太清楚你有
something on here I don't know we've
我不知道我们在这里
never actually got that far let's see oh
从来没有那么遥远，让我们看看哦
yeah that's true oh come on there's
是的，是的，哦，来吧
nothing there
那里空无一物
that's probably why
那可能就是为什么
excuse you single quote right sure
请问单引号正确吗
I don't write C point anymore I don't
我不再写C点了
remember any of these oh there we go
记住其中任何一个哦，我们走了
yeah somehow we've got that and there
是的，我们已经知道了
yep the query I had in there
是我在那里的查询
yeah those reservations that's right
是的，那些保留是正确的
yeah restart ok you should see the new
是的，重新启动，确定，您应该会看到新的
updates there yep
是的，在那里更新
already so now we're using the spring
已经如此，现在我们正在使用Spring
theatre source properties to limit the
剧院源属性以限制
connections in oh not bad okay now I
连接在哦，还不错吧，现在我
like sequel I think it's got a future
像续集一样，我认为这是有未来的
just yeah it's controversial but but
是的，这是有争议的，但是
let's be honest if we're on a if we're
说实话，如果我们在
on a platform like Google Cloud I want
在我想要的Google Cloud这样的平台上
some of that Google willy wonka factory
某些Google Willy Wonka工厂
magic man I don't want to just anybody
魔术师，我不想只是任何人
can spit up a sequel data store that's
可以吐出续集的数据存储
coming true what do you what do you got
成为现实，你有什么？
that like how can i you take it up a
就像我怎么能拿起它
notch what's what's a really compelling
刻划什么才是真正令人信服的
offering here I've heard things your
提供在这里我听到了你的事情
things
东西
yeah about about so I think what you
是的，所以我想你
heard so with sequel server of course
当然是用续集服务器听到的
you're running like everybody knows how
你像每个人都知道怎么跑
to use these my sequin post-crisis and
用这些我在危机后的亮片
all these services but they are
所有这些服务，但它们是
typically going to be restricted into a
通常会被限制为
single zone so in the cloud you have the
单一区域，因此在云中您拥有
zone in which participates in the region
参与该区域的区域
and the region may have multiple zones
该区域可能有多个区域
that's really close by and then you have
真的很近，然后你有
multiple regions within like like an
像
area like Europe who have multiple
像欧洲这样的地区，有多个
multiple regions here but then if you
这里有多个区域，但是如果您
actually need to spin out your data to
实际需要分拆数据以
across the world then having a single a
然后在世界范围内只有一个
single single instance doesn't really
单个实例不是真的
work anymore right as soon as I do that
我一开始就马上工作
I run into problems with like
我遇到了类似的问题
consistency of my data rek'sai right on
我的数据的一致性rek'sai对
the cap theorem right so some cases some
上限定理是正确的，所以在某些情况下
people do is to use something like a no
人们要做的是使用诸如否
sequel server right and then you try to
续集服务器权利，然后您尝试
span this across across the world now
现在遍及全球
did you know Josh light is actually
你知道乔希的光芒是真的吗
really really slow it is slow yeah it's
真的很慢，很慢，是的
actually slower than I expected in fact
实际上比我预期的要慢
I didn't realize this until I talked to
我直到与我交谈才意识到
my colleague James Ward who told me did
我的同事詹姆斯·沃德（James Ward）告诉我
you know a round trip between like
你知道像
America in Japan with just light is
美国在日本的光是
actually about 70 milliseconds 70
实际上大约70毫秒70
milliseconds that's very low for latency
毫秒数，这对于延迟而言非常低
right so that's where you get into all
对，所以这就是您进入所有领域的地方
these consistent issue now what we have
这些一致的问题，现在我们拥有
is something called spanner
是所谓的扳手
or Klaus better which is a distributed
或Klaus更好的是分布式
database so we can run spanner in
数据库，以便我们可以在其中运行扳手
original way so you can run it just in
原始方式，因此您可以直接运行
Europe or you can run in a globally
欧洲或您可以在全球范围内运行
distributed way where you have spanner
您有扳手的分布式方式
instances across the world in Asia in
在亚洲的全球实例
European America and the data will be
欧洲和数据将
automatically replicated for you and we
自动为您复制，我们
can actually do strong consistency even
甚至可以做到很强的一致性
in this multi regional setting that's
在这个多区域环境中
just pure magic to me and the one of the
对我来说只是纯粹的魔法之一
reasons why this will work is because of
之所以会奏效的原因是
the atomic clock that we actually have
我们实际拥有的原子钟
in the data center so in order to get
在数据中心，以便获得
really really accurate timing of what
真正非常准确的时间安排
when things are happening we actually
当事情发生时，我们实际上
have atomic clocks that's actually keyed
有实际上被锁上的原子钟
to the geolocation of the data center
到数据中心的地理位置
which is quite amazing now to use
现在使用起来非常神奇
spanner it's actually really really
扳手实际上是真的真的
simple and straightforward if you have
简单直接
an existing application like this one
像这样的现有应用程序
what I'm going to do is to yeah let me
我要做的是，是的，让我
see here yeah it's nesting okay so what
看到这里，是的，嵌套好吗
I'm going to do is to just get enough
我要做的就是得到足够的
support for now so I'm going to get rid
现在支持，所以我要摆脱
of the strata here so maybe I don't want
这里的地层，所以也许我不想
sequel what's up we're not using the
续集最新消息，我们没有使用
post or you can just oh yeah okay yeah
发布或者您可以哦，是的，是的，是的
so let's keep going
所以我们继续前进
so let's see here maybe I am going to
所以让我们看看这里，也许我要去
just come on the code right so I'm going
只是正确输入代码，所以我要
to fine I'm gonna come in this alpha now
好吧，我现在要进入这个阿尔法
because I don't want I don't want the
因为我不想我不想
secret stuff right now okay so let's do
秘密的东西，现在好了，让我们做
that okay and then for the reservation
好的，然后再预约
here okay component okay okay yeah okay
这里好，组件好，好，是的，好
all right so so this one I'm going to do
好的，所以我要去做
this I'm going to copy and paste this
这个我要复制并粘贴这个
whole thing oh yeah okay so now I have
整件事哦，是的，现在我有了
got all right so I'm gonna do a span a
没事，所以我要跨度
demo right here
演示在这里
yes all right so we're going to keep the
是的，好的，我们将继续
same class here with the static class
这里与静态类相同
but we're going to you what we're going
但是我们要向你
to do object mapping directly from
直接从中进行对象映射
reservation to a sprain database okay so
保留扭伤数据库就可以了
we are going to try this out so spinner
我们将尝试这个，所以微调
demo right here okay so we're going to
演示在这里好，所以我们要
try this out
试试这个
okay so well the easiest thing to do is
好吧，最简单的方法是
to added this destroy before it so we do
在此之前添加此销毁，所以我们这样做
have a cloud spanner starter which I can
有一个我可以的云启动器
use like this is code that data
像这样使用的是数据的代码
data spinner right here okay and of
数据微调器就可以了
course we'd only specify the version
当然，我们只指定版本
because all the versions are being
因为所有版本都在
managed by the bomb so that's all you
由炸弹管理，仅此而已
need to do now with spinner of course
当然需要现在使用微调器
you need an instance we're going to go
你需要一个实例，我们要去
ahead and create a new spending instance
并创建一个新的支出实例
with a new database and a schema okay so
有了新的数据库和架构就可以了
we're gonna do that hopefully fairly
我们希望公平地做到这一点
quickly so if I go back to my console
快速，所以如果我回到控制台
here I can go and find the spanner
在这里我可以找到扳手
resource right here and you really have
资源在这里，你真的有
a reservations created but you know what
创建了预订，但您知道吗
Josh I'm going to spend your unlimited
乔希，我要花你无限的时间
dollars here so I'm going to say spring
美元在这里，我要说春天
demo something like that right so that's
演示类似的东西，所以
the instance the new sinsemilla and then
实例是新的西塞米利亚，然后
here we can of course pick whether we
在这里我们当然可以选择是否
want original instance or multi-regional
想要原始实例或多区域
instance okay what do you think so the
实例好吧，您如何看待
multi-regional instance we can spend
我们可以花费的多区域实例
across North America Europe in Asia
横跨北美欧洲在亚洲
isn't that a horizontal band yes it's
那不是一个水平乐队吗？
not north and south but it's yeah
不是南北，而是
exactly yeah and we can run one noting
是的，我们可以注意一下
one of the new choppa zones or at the
新的斩波区之一或
region and we can just go multi-regional
地区，我们可以走多地区
highly available sounds like a lot but
高可用声音听起来很多，但
that's like lattes well we're gonna be
就像拿铁一样，我们会成为
done with she's talking like 40 minutes
她说了40分钟就完成了
so it wouldn't be that much that's fine
所以就没那么多了
yeah so let me go ahead and create a new
是的，让我继续创建一个新的
database here in Kuwait the reservations
数据库在科威特的保留
is that what we did yeah I've got enough
是我们所做的，是的，我受够了
money to last me the rest of my life as
钱可以让我终生
long as I di next Tuesday
只要我下个星期二
well let's now hope that and that's not
好吧，现在让我们希望那不是
what's going to happen all right
会发生什么事
typical reservation and as you can see
典型的预订，如您所见
everything's groovy driven if you want
如果需要的话，一切都是时髦的
to if you want it right so I'm gonna say
如果你想对的话我就说
the primary key now in spanner you don't
现在您不需要扳手中的主键
want to use the auto increment ID
想要使用自动增量ID
because that it's not very good for its
因为它不是很好
ability debase what you want to do is
能力使你想做的是
using a UID that's actually randomly
使用实际上是随机的UID
generated in fact anything that's
实际上产生的任何东西
increasing monotonically is not a good
单调增加不是一个好习惯
idea spender because in some of these
想法花费者，因为其中一些
databases you're going to run into hot
您将遇到热的数据库
spotting for that matter okay so in what
发现这个问题好吗
else you got here reservation name name
否则你在这里预订名称名称
of the reservation okay I'm gonna make
我要预约的
that a string as well okay and then we
那个字符串也可以，然后我们
can set the primary key as ID now of
现在可以将主键设置为ID
course if you don't want to do this in
当然，如果您不想这样做
the GUI every time you need to create
每次需要创建GUI时
the database you can use this
您可以使用的数据库
EEMA as well right and that looks
EEMA也是正确的，看起来
remarkably sequel like yep that is
像是的惊人续集
because span is actually a relational
因为跨度实际上是一个关系
database it's not a no sequel by say
数据库不是说可以的续集
globally distributed highly available
全球分布的高可用性
strongly consistent sequel database yes
高度一致的续集数据库是
yeah yeah
是啊
so let me go ahead and create this new
所以让我继续创建这个新的
instance and the new table okay so let's
实例和新表还可以，所以让我们
see create so just remember what
看到创建，所以只记得什么
happened I just created a globally
碰巧我刚刚创建了一个全球
distributed database and she created the
分布式数据库，她创建了
table for it and now let's go ahead and
表，现在让我们继续前进，
see what we can do to make this work so
看看我们能做些什么来使这项工作如此
for reservation we can use the spinner
进行预订，我们可以使用微调器
annotation here with let's call table oh
让我们在这里标注表哦
did it not bringing the hood eco it the
它没有带来引擎盖生态它
palm guards no rebuild
棕榈卫士不重建
is there a reboot word more of a auto
有重启词更多的自动
import let's try to import a little bit
导入让我们尝试导入一点
you know and if Oh things fails if
你知道，如果哦，事情失败了，如果
there's a issue with the import that's
导入存在问题
right here maven clinging in package
就在这里，行家紧紧包裹着
sure and it's just make sure the palm is
当然，只是要确保手掌是
good right we need to download a few
好的，我们需要下载一些
things here okay
事情还好吧
well the test works but that's because
测试很好，但这是因为
we have a retaining code yet okay yeah
我们有一个保留代码，还可以
so let's go ahead and imitate this class
所以让我们继续模仿这个课程
and where's my table annotation that
我的表注释在哪里
should be here table table table hmm I'm
应该在这里桌子桌子桌子桌子我
stable thank you yeah well do you have
稳定，谢谢，你有吗
to go back to your meeting don't know
回到你的会议不知道
until the Refresh I think it really okay
直到刷新，我认为真的还好
all right let's try this again
好吧，让我们再试一次
zero no it's not still yeah maven Andrey
零不，还不是吗，行家安德烈
important yes okay hopefully this is
重要的是，好的，希望这是
going to find it because without the
要找到它，因为没有
table annotation oh there we go all
表格注解噢，我们走了
right very nice yeah so and this will of
对，非常好，是的，这将
course infer the nyan reservation will
当然会推断出nyan保留会
be the table name and is that the one
是表名，是那个
that I created yeah but if you want to
是我创造的，但是如果你想
change the table name you can as well as
更改表名称，您也可以
I'm going to call it reservation just so
我将其称为保留
you know you can remap this now further
你知道你现在可以重新映射
for the ID rather than the integer
ID而不是整数
remember we changed it to a string so we
记得我们将其更改为字符串，所以我们
can store UUID and then for marking
可以存储UUID，然后进行标记
primary keys now in spanner we actually
现在扳手中的主键实际上
can't handle what we call a composite
无法处理我们所说的复合材料
so we're going to use a primary key
所以我们将使用主键
notation then you can actually mark
表示法，然后您可以实际标记
multiple columns as primary key if you
如果您将多列用作主键
want to but right now which is a one
想但现在是一个
okay good yeah pretty good and then to
好的，很好，然后
access this database of course you can
当然可以访问该数据库
use we have a spanner template just
使用我们有一个扳手模板
similar to the JDBC template but we can
与JDBC模板类似，但是我们可以
do even more
做更多
we actually have full sprint data
我们实际上有完整的冲刺数据
integration as well so we can do data
集成以及我们可以做数据
repositories ah yeah yeah no Dickens
仓库啊是否狄更斯
no no Josh I do need your help to get
不，不，乔什，我确实需要您的帮助才能得到
sprint data repository in here I think I
我认为我在这里冲刺数据仓库
can never remember the name for it but I
永远不记得它的名字，但我
want the rice one yeah
要一碗饭
sorry there neither I actually need the
抱歉，我实际上都不需要
rest part is free though can we do the
其余部分是免费的，尽管我们可以做到
rest repository because if you want to
休息库，因为如果你想
expose the repository in CRE D restful
在CRE D Restful中公开存储库
manner you can actually do the rest
你实际上可以做到的方式
repository as well having usually for a
仓库通常也有一个
while not a Mongol one okay very cool
虽然不是蒙古人，还可以，很酷
works yeah I think that worked there
是的，我认为那是可行的
just in case we do a green port again
以防万一我们再次做一个绿色港口
okay so if I go back to the Spenard
好吧，如果我回到斯本纳德
database sorry the spinner code we
数据库对不起微调器代码，我们
should be able to do something like this
应该能够做这样的事情
we're going to say oh we're gonna find
我们会说哦，我们会找到
out pretty soon yeah
很快就要出来了
living on the edge right repository
生活在边缘右边的仓库
expands and we can of course use the the
扩展，我们当然可以使用
spinner repository but we can also
微调存储库，但我们也可以
automatically infer that because we're
自动推断，因为我们
using spending this project we can just
使用这个项目，我们可以
use the page in sorting repository as
将页面用于排序存储库
well and then we can give the name of
好，然后我们可以给
the reservation and the ID type as well
预订和ID类型
and that is all you need to do now if
这就是您现在需要做的
you wanna oh right I see what you mean
你想哦，对了，我明白你的意思了
and if you want to expose this as a
如果您想将其公开为
restful endpoint you can just do
你可以做的宁静的终点
repository repository price controller
仓库价格控制器
or yeah resource yeah but yeah like Josh
还是资源丰富，但是像乔希一样
said I'm not quite sure what this is
说我不太清楚这是什么
going to work as an asset class no you
要作为资产类别工作，不是吗
don't think so I think we've done
不要以为我想我们已经完成了
outside yeah okay so let's go ahead and
在外面，好吧，让我们继续前进，
just move this outwards ah da without
只是向外移动这个啊啊，没有
work better okay that's good happy yeah
做得更好，好开心，是的
Josh happy then I think I'll be happy
乔希开心，那我想我会开心
too sorry
太抱歉了
checked it in here and yep data okay so
在这里检查并确认数据还可以
we can write something not work you know
我们可以写一些行不通的东西，你知道
what let's just run it and then we can
让我们来运行它，然后我们可以
see that we can see the restful endpoint
看到我们可以看到宁静的终点
and that we can put the data in that way
并且我们可以以这种方式放置数据
so I'm gonna stop it wrong and hopefully
所以我会阻止它并希望
this will work
这会工作
how many people think this would you
有多少人认为这会你
start up with the creb resource we can
从我们可以使用的垃圾资源开始
just write data to a globally through
只需通过
this system Wow yeah well we're gonna
这个系统哇，好吧，我们要
see well at least your sequel demos feel
至少可以很好地看到续集演示
works that's good no yeah big fan I can
作品很好，是的，我可以
say that sequel stuffs it's probably
说续集的东西可能是
gonna be big one day yeah yeah I think
有一天会很大，是的，我想
it's still big today all right so you do
今天还很大，所以你可以
have the web resource right so we should
拥有正确的网络资源，所以我们应该
be able to do something like this we can
能够做这样的事情，我们可以
curl localhost:8080
curl本地主机：8080
yes right oh look oh hey look there's
是的，对，哦，看，哦，嘿，看
reservations for me API that's pretty
对我来说很漂亮的API
good so if I do reservations Oh what
好，所以如果我保留的话
happened oh you know what happened it's
发生了哦，你知道发生了什么事
because I didn't really connect we
因为我没有真正联系我们
didn't specify which spending instance I
没有指定我使用哪个支出实例
want to connect you right it was a CLE
想要连接您，这是CLE
so we do need to configure my
所以我们需要配置我的
reservation instance right so it's
预留实例正确，所以
called spring demo actually and then for
其实叫spring demo然后
spanner dot let's see here database name
扳手点让我们在这里看到数据库名称
is Koh reservations right and then we're
是Koh保留的权利，然后我们
going to talk to the reservation table
要和预订表谈谈
right then just make sure I got
那就确保我知道了
everything right
一切正常
all right let's restart this so for
好吧，让我们重新启动它，以便
those of you who didn't raise your hand
那些没有举手的人
that good for you
对你有好处
that didn't work the first time no I
第一次没有用
yeah now to test out this end point I'm
是的，现在测试这个终点
going to do something else I'm going to
我要去做别的事情
create a test I HTTP I don't know if
创建一个我不知道的HTTP测试
you've done this before
你以前做过
but in here we can zoom in a little bit
但在这里我们可以放大一点
I'm going to get do a getter right so
我要正确地做一个吸气剂
I'm going to do I get let's see here
我要去做，让我们看看这里
8080 and let's just go ahead and get
8080，让我们继续前进
prisons and see if we can this thing
监狱，看看我们能不能做这件事
knows oh oh
知道哦哦
reservation sorry yeah now that one
保留对不起，现在那一个
right reservations right okay so we do
正确的预订好吧，我们这样做
purple one all right so it's actually
紫色一个好吧，所以实际上
stopping my connection to the spinner
停止与微调器的连接
instance which I just created and the
我刚创建的实例和
first request is a little slow just
第一个请求有点慢
because of the instant the connection is
由于连接瞬间
being established and we're actually in
建立起来，我们实际上在
oh my goodness like I'm very happy this
哦，天哪，我很高兴
actually working so let's go ahead and
实际工作，所以让我们继续前进，
post something into this database I'm
将一些内容发布到该数据库中
going to say
要说
we post reservations reservations okay
我们发布预订预订好吗
and then we have an ID now remember we
然后我们有一个ID现在记得我们
needed to use UID so it's not make
需要使用UID，所以它不会
something up doesn't matter and then we
没关系，然后我们
have a name I'm gonna say reservation
有个名字我要说保留
for Josh all right
对于乔希没事
and that's just you're on the list so
那就是你在名单上，所以
let's do a post and this just wrote the
让我们做一个帖子，这只是写了
day they are the data into this global
那天他们是这个全球的数据
disability database and if I go back to
残疾数据库，如果我回到
the database console and if everything
数据库控制台，如果一切
worked out properly I can go see
工作正常我可以去看看
reservation I just created it if I go
预订我刚创建的话就去了
see data come on
看到数据来了
oh there we go sweet nectar not bad yeah
哦，我们去了甜蜜的花蜜，还不错
pretty good right that's the first time
不错，这是第一次
I've ever been part of something a cool
我曾经参加过很酷的事情
just remind you now you have a global
只是提醒您，现在您有了全球
distributed database what that mean also
分布式数据库又意味着什么
means is that you can actually run your
意味着您可以实际运行
application across the globe in a multi
遍及全球的应用
regional fashion pretty easily as well
区域时尚也很容易
for two lattes an hour yeah all right so
一小时两个拿铁是的，所以
good stuff I like that yeah we can't I
好东西，我喜欢，是的，我们不能
love the fact that it's globally
喜欢它在全球范围内的事实
distributed but practically speaking I'm
分散但实际上我是
not gonna want to give out the
不想放弃
credentials to my spanner database to
我的扳手数据库凭证
everybody with whom I want to
我想和每个人在一起
communicate right I'm probably still
正确沟通，我可能还是
gonna need to have some of those more
需要更多一些
traditional approaches to integration
传统的整合方法
and for that I think messaging is a
为此，我认为消息传递是一种
really fine choice right what I'm going
很好的选择，正确的选择
to show next is Google clouds pub/sub
接下来要显示的是Google cloud pub / sub
support now pub/sub is a you can think
现在支持pub / sub是您可以想到的
of it as a message queue but it's not
它作为消息队列，但不是
right it's it's make it smaller and
正确的是它变得更小
actually Google search I don't know if
其实我不知道Google搜索
you know this people but Google has a
你认识这个人，但是Google有一个
side business doing search and you can
进行搜索的副业，您可以
search within the console to write and
在控制台中搜索以编写和
it works
有用
it's okay I mean we'll see with we'll
没关系，我的意思是我们会看到
see how they go but you found pops up
看看他们怎么走，但你发现弹出
this so there's my existing topic in in
这就是我现有的主题
the pub sub you've got the idea of a
pub sub，你有一个想法
topic to which you publish messages and
您向其发布消息的主题，以及
you have a subscription from which you
您有一个订阅，从中
consume messages right so I've got the
正确使用消息，所以我得到了
subscription here it's called
订阅在这里叫做
reservation subscription the the thing
预订预订的东西
it's connected to is called reservations
它连接到称为保留
so I'm gonna use that in my code here in
所以我要在我的代码中使用它
order to do that I have some
为了做到这一点，我有一些
configuration required to think yes yep
认为是需要配置
but you do need to add the pub sub
但是您确实需要添加pub sub
starter to your app life
开启您的应用人生
okay palm that XML just copy and paste
好吧，XML只是复制和粘贴
this oh actually you got it right here
哦，实际上你在这里
they're mine I'm off to the radio yeah
他们是我的，我要去广播电台
because the reason in Syria is because
因为在叙利亚的原因是因为
he added GCP messaging when he used to
他以前习惯于添加GCP消息传递
read the star that spring died oh yeah
读到春天死去的星星哦，是的
happiest place on earth
地球上最幸福的地方
all right okay public void publish
好的，可以，公共无效，发布
they're actually pub/sub and I'm gonna
他们实际上是酒吧/订票员，我要
do something a little silly I'm gonna
做些愚蠢的事
create an example that publishes and
创建一个发布并
sends messages in the same application
在同一应用程序中发送消息
which is a little weird
这有点奇怪
normally you'd have two things separated
通常你会把两件事分开
crossed by a network boundary and they
越过网络边界，他们
should communicate with each other that
应该互相沟通
way but you know Yolo so private final
方式，但是你知道Yolo这么私人决赛
pub/sub subscriber operations or
发布/订阅者操作​​或
template subscribe and we want the same
模板订阅，我们希望相同
thing but for publisher right okay
事情，但对出版商来说还可以
publisher alright and we want this to be
发行人还可以，我们希望成为
injected into the constructor so I'll
注入到构造函数中，所以我将
use Lombok to make sure look at that and
使用龙目岛（Lombok）确保查看
what I'm doing something I'm gonna
我正在做的事
register a subscriber first so I'm gonna
首先注册一个订户，我要
listen on the subscription side that's
在订阅方面
called reservations subscription that's
称为预订订阅的
right yeah come on there you go okay and
是的，来吧，你还可以，
I'm gonna register a new consumer sweet
我要注册一个新的消费者甜食
nectar and I want to get the message so
花蜜，我想得到这样的信息
I have to acknowledge this right back or
我必须承认这一点，否则
neck right right don't acknowledge it
脖子右边右边不承认
always remember to do that if you intend
一定要记住，如果您打算这样做
to keep the message consumed and then
保持消息消耗，然后
I'm gonna get the message and we get to
我会收到消息，然后我们去
the data and then turn that into a
数据，然后将其转换为
string into a UTF a string to string
将字符串转换为UTF将字符串转换为字符串
utf-8 string in there we go yep okay so
utf-8字符串在那里，我们可以，所以
there's my message already good stuff
我的留言已经好东西了
and I'm gonna log that out and I'll say
我要注销了，我会说
logged on info and I'm gonna use my
登录信息，我将使用我的
logger my trusty log4j logger which has
记录器我值得信赖的log4j记录器
never left me it's dutifully there new
从未离开过我，尽职尽责
message okay good stuff now on that's
消息好吧，现在的好东西是
the consumer I'm gonna register that and
我要注册的消费者
then I'll publish a message to myself a
然后我会向自己发布一条消息
very sad thing to do you think about it
你想起来很伤心
it's a message in a bottle so I'm gonna
这是一个装在瓶子里的信息，所以我要
leave I'm gonna send a message to the
离开，我要向
message in this case you're just gonna
在这种情况下的消息，你只是
be a string I could its I unpacked a
是一个字符串，我可以将其解压缩
string on this side but it doesn't have
在这边的字符串，但它没有
to be a
成为一个
strain the pub/sub message has bytes it
应变pub / sub消息有字节
could be whatever right I could even use
可能是我什至可以使用的任何权利
it as a string and use JSON if I wanted
将其作为字符串并使用JSON（如果需要）
to but in this case I'm just gonna say
但在这种情况下，我只是要说
[Music]
[音乐]
okay okay so let's see okay looks good
好吧好吧，让我们看看好看起来不错
to you yeah okay
对你，好吧
I should have stashed that to the side
我本该藏在一边
yeah you know there's there's no risk in
是的，你知道那里没有风险
our demo you know that's such a fool
我们的演示，你知道那太傻了
fool proof demo I have no fear about our
傻瓜演示，我不用担心我们的
demo doing massively distributed systems
演示做大规模分布式系统
connected into cloud infrastructure of
连接到的云基础架构
thousands of miles away that I have
我有千里之外
every doubt world I have every
每个我拥有的怀疑世界
confidence will work but unicode but you
信心会奏效，但unicode但您
know but you did say to you TFA strings
知道，但您确实对您说过TFA字符串
so didn't work huh what happened what
所以没用吧，发生了什么事
are you looking for yes okay
你在找是好吗
oh yeah it has to be got it upside down
哦，是的，必须颠倒过来
yeah I see you can't just I think you
是的，我明白你不能只是我想你
can use type I know no I mean it's not
可以使用我不知道的类型
the same thing you could but you would
同样的事情你可以，但是你会
be wrong okay anyway so so did it work
反正好吧，所以它起作用了
here we go I got a message nice you do
在这里，我们走了，我收到一条消息，你很高兴
have a message vanish how cool is that
有消息消失那是多么酷
that is pretty awesome it's like having
那真是太棒了
a pen pal from Spain which is myself
来自西班牙的笔友是我自己
good study yeah not bad that's really
很好的学习，是的，还不错
good
好
also that's gonna be big help me scale
这也将极大地帮助我扩展
okay yeah that was pretty easy I think
好吧，是的，我认为这很容易
that you know at this point we've kind
在这一点上你知道我们很友善
of exhausted all the really cool things
精疲力尽
that Google can help me with it's not
Google可以帮助我的不是
like you have some sort of artificial
就像你有某种人造的
intelligence that I can use to read
我可以用来阅读的智力
pictures or whatever right no really no
图片或其他权利，没有，真的没有
yeah well actually but you have a
是的，实际上，但是你有一个
picture we can tell you what's in the
图片，我们可以告诉你其中的内容
picture so you do have this intelligence
图片，所以你确实有这种智慧
yeah it's actually pretty smart
是的，实际上很聪明
yeah do you only keep it a try it yeah
是的，您只能尝试一下吗
it's really nice but the 14e that you
真的很好，但是14e
need to put the picture somewhere okay
需要将图片放在适当的位置
okay so so there are a number of places
好，所以有很多地方
where you can store like binary blocks
您可以在其中存储二进制块
right so you imagine you're writing a
对，所以您想像您正在写
new application you need to store audio
您需要存储音频的新应用程序
photo videos or whatever then maybe you
照片视频或其他任何东西，也许你
can you know put it you don't want to
你知道吗，你不想
put out in just a VM on the disk because
放在磁盘上的虚拟机中，因为
then that this will run out of space
那么这将耗尽空间
Google Cloud you can put it into our
您可以将Google Cloud放入我们的
storage koku cough storage it's really
储存国库咳嗽储存真的
just a bucket store so you can store
只是一个水桶店，所以你可以存储
just as much as binary data blobs as you
和您一样多的二进制数据斑点
want and you don't really have to worry
想要，而您真的不必担心
about these sizes at all because as you
关于这些大小，因为就像你
say manage servers for us okay so I
说为我们管理服务器好，所以我
think Josh you I think I sent you some
以为乔希，你我想我给你发了一些
pictures over here
这里的图片
okay on right now are you trying to
好吧，现在您是否要
airdrop from your phone to the
从手机空投到
presentation right now yep yeah so so we
演示文稿是的，是的，所以我们
do have two pictures here we have a dog
这里有两张照片，我们有一只狗
in the cat okay well you all rename that
在猫里面，好吧，你们都重命名了
to yeah yeah okay that means that by
对，是的，这意味着
process of elimination and I need that
消除的过程，我需要
because that's a dog yeah I took the
因为那是一条狗，是的，我带了
photo off both of these photos
关闭这两张照片
unfortunately I don't have any of the
不幸的是，我没有任何
pets so that's kind of sad okay so now
宠物，所以有点难过，所以现在
where do I so you can go to yeah you can
我在哪里可以去呀，你可以
go to Google College story
前往Google College故事
got it yeah it is where you can store
是的，这是您可以存储的地方
the binary data now you can create a
现在可以创建二进制数据了
bucket so buckets the top-level storage
进行存储，以便存储顶级存储
with globally unique so you can give it
具有全球唯一性，因此您可以给它
whatever name that you want you can
无论你想要什么名字
again choose whether it's original or a
再次选择是原始的还是
multi-regional depends on your need okay
多地区取决于您的需要
and the bucket name has to be unique
并且存储桶名称必须唯一
global okay so go ahead and just say
全球还可以，所以继续说
create got it yeah in the pocket you can
是的，可以放在口袋里
create more directories if you want to
如果要创建更多目录
you where I can just drag and drop your
你在哪里我可以拖放你的
files into weight actually it's jpg is a
文件变成重量，实际上它的jpg是一个
jpg yeah should be okay I mean I'll
jpg是的应该没事，我是说
forget I don't quite remember what I
忘记我不太记得我在做什么
took the photos ass but yeah okay cool
拍了照片的屁股，但是很好
uploading nice very nice and now you can
上传非常好，现在您可以
use spring to actually read the sub ops
使用spring实际阅读子操作
now you can either use the Google
现在您可以使用Google
quality API to do it but we actually
高质量的API可以做到，但实际上
have really nice abstraction layer code
有非常好的抽象层代码
GCP well with the screen resource right
GCP屏幕资源正确
so I think we already have those
所以我认为我们已经有了那些
serratus already right
锯齿已经正确
I hope yeah I hope it's already there
我希望是的，我希望它已经在那里
yeah and what you can do is to use the
是的，您可以使用
the URI like that starts with G s colon
像这样的URI以G冒号开头
slash slash and then you can point that
斜线斜线然后你可以指出
to the bucket in the file location
到文件位置中的存储桶
directly GS yep slash slash exactly
直接GS是斜杠斜杠
flanimals yep and then slash yeah and
是的，然后是斜线，是的，
maybe the cat jpg PG okay and that'll be
也许猫jpg PG好了，那将会是
a resource there will be a spring
资源将有春天
resource exactly so you don't have to
完全是资源，因此您不必
use the lower level API from the from
使用from中的较低级别的API
google cloud you can just use the
谷歌云，你可以只使用
resource abstraction if you want to
资源抽象，如果您想
right okay good
好吧好
you see why you check both often yeah
你明白为什么经常检查
okay now I've got I mean it's B it's
好吧，现在我知道我的意思是B
cool that I can inject them and stuff
很酷，我可以注入它们和东西
but yeah what do i what do I actually
但是是的，我到底该怎么办
want to do with that what what could I
想要这样做我该怎么办
do
做
okay how could I analyze this yeah so to
好吧，我怎么能分析这个，所以
analyze this you can use our vision API
对此进行分析，您可以使用我们的视觉API
okay so to do that you need to you can
好吧，这样做，你需要你可以
of course again use our clarity to do it
当然，再次使用我们的清晰度来做到这一点
or you can just add a vision starter as
或者您也可以添加一个视觉入门
well so we do need to add it into your
好吧，我们确实需要将其添加到您的
palm the XML this time okay yeah so in
这次可以使用XML了，是的，所以
the starters right so you can see we try
入门者正确，所以您可以看到我们尝试
to make this a lot very very easy for
使这变得非常非常容易
folks to use Rice's yeah starter vision
人们使用赖斯的“入门”愿景
I think easy
我觉得很简单
okay private final cloud vision template
好的私有最终云愿景模板
that's the one yeah so behind the scenes
那是幕后幕布
we automatically configure again your
我们会自动再次配置您的
credentials we stop with your API
凭证，我们将停止使用您的API
connection we give you this really nice
连接，我们给你这个真的很好
abstract way to access a template this
访问模板的抽象方式
template it goes template good stuff
它去模板好东西
yeah and when when the application
是的，何时申请
starts up show you process it okay yeah
启动显示您对其进行处理，是的
sure so you can say I need to store
可以，所以你可以说我需要存储
those resources as well so I find the
这些资源也是，所以我发现
final resource cat dog okay
最终资源猫狗还可以
this cat equals cat this done dog
这只猫等于这只成猫狗
giggles dog void analyze throws
咯咯笑的狗无效分析抛出
exceptions okay so this that template I
例外，好了，这个模板我
guess right yeah a mais image yep
猜对了，是的，是的，是的
there's only one yeah yeah and you know
只有一个是的，你知道
you can select the different things you
您可以选择不同的东西
want to detect so if you zoom in here a
要检测，所以如果您放大此处
little bit we have label detection we
一点点，我们有标签检测
can detect landmarks we can see where
可以发现地标，我们可以看到
the facial features are for example
面部特征例如
right well we can even do OCR so if
好吧，我们甚至可以进行OCR，所以如果
there is text in the picture we can
图片中有文字我们可以
actually extract it for you so you can
实际为您提取它，以便您可以
know what is actually in the photos so
知道照片中实际上是什么
what am I looking for here so for us
我在这里找什么，对我们来说
we're just going to you let's do the the
我们只是去找你，让我们做
label detection so this is going to beat
标签检测，所以这将击败
it be able to tell you what is actually
能够告诉你实际上是什么
in the photo or the picture that you
在您的照片或图片中
have okay then it's going to give you a
好的，那会给你一个
response then you do you are you can do
回应，那么你就是你可以做到的
two calls right with the lower level API
使用较低级别的API进行两次调用
you can do a batch analyzation so you
您可以进行批量分析，以便
can sending multiple multiple files and
可以发送多个文件，并且
you can get multiple responses back as
您可以将多个回复
well and so what I want to do is on
好，所以我想做的是
announce what I got back sure from that
宣布我从中得到的肯定
I'm gonna say so you can't just print it
我要说，所以你不能只打印它
only if you want to yeah okay why is
只有当你想是的，为什么
this unhappy I don't need that
这种不快乐，我不需要
I just need log4j okay good and log cat
我只需要log4j好，然后登录
cat response dot to stream maybe yeah
猫回应点流也许
sure
当然
long dot info
长点信息
good yep and dog responds okay ready
是的，狗很好回应
yeah yeah this is too easy
是的，这太简单了
it is pretty easy yeah but the response
是的，这很容易，但是响应
how you get back is if it works yeah if
你怎么回来的是，如果有效的话
it works yes if it works yeah I think
如果有效，是的，是的，我想
it's going to be pretty impressive
这将是非常令人印象深刻的
especially if you never have done
特别是如果你从未做过
machine learning in the past inward just
过去的机器学习只是向内
don't want to deal with the machine
不想处理机器
learning code yourself all have api's to
自己学习代码都可以使用api
use yeah so here's the dog yeah yeah so
用呀，这是狗呀，所以
the dog is 99 percent sure that it was a
那只狗百分之九十九确定那是狗
dog right okay so it's got a score 99
狗好吧，总分99
percent yaagh
百分率
yeah it's 99 percent that's a pug which
是的，这是99％的哈巴狗
is pretty right 98 percent that it's a
是非常正确的98％
mammal dog it's a pretty sure that's a
哺乳动物的狗很确定
vertebrate which is good yeah Kent k9 k
很好的脊椎动物肯特k9 k
nice yeah sort yeah dog breed it's now
是的，很好，是的，是狗的品种，现在
that is true I don't know yeah it's got
是的，我不知道是的
skin okay Google now one I'm not quite
皮肤还可以，谷歌现在我还不太
sure why that's here but maybe five
确定为什么会在这里，但也许五个
percent chance that's pretty good that's
非常好的机会百分比是
pretty good yeah it's got a nose awesome
很好，它的鼻子很棒
yeah so you can space it by how many of
是的，所以您可以将其间隔多少
these labels you want to get back I
这些标签你想找我
think by people would give you ten let's
认为别人会给你十个
take a look at the cat and it's it's a
看看那只猫，那是一个
the cat is a cat it's a mammal and it's
那只猫是一只猫，它是一种哺乳动物，它是
a small to medium sized cat that's right
一只对的中小型猫
it's a feline it's got whiskers it's an
这是猫科动物，有胡须，这是
Aegean cat what does that mean it's like
爱琴海猫是什么意思
from Greece or something or that region
来自希腊或其他地区
I don't know um carnivores short haired
我不知道嗯食肉动物短发
cat domestic European Shorthair oh good
猫家欧洲短毛猫哦好
stuff and it's got a snout as well just
东西，还有一个鼻子
like the mom yeah yeah that's pretty
就像妈妈，是的，很漂亮
cool right okay okay so we've got all
酷吧，好吧，好吧，我们都拥有了
this cool stuff yeah of course in the
这个很酷的东西，当然在
software that I build nothing ever goes
我一无所获的软件一去不复返
wrong but I'm sure for you in your
错了，但是我敢肯定你在
software there might be errors will be
软件可能会出现错误
personal yeah absolutely
绝对是个人的
great so what would you recommend for
太好了，您会推荐什么
those who would like you yeah
那些想要你的人
occasionally run into issues in
偶尔遇到问题
production so there are a few things you
生产，所以有几件事你
can use on Google Cloud well first of
首先可以很好地在Google Cloud上使用
all if your beauty microservices and one
如果您有美容微服务和一项
server is calling each other I say if
服务器互相呼叫我说如果
you have a rest controller that uses the
您有一个使用
rest and play to cause something else
休息并玩耍导致其他事情
you kind of want to trace in you know
你想追踪你知道
understand who is actually only what and
了解谁实际上只是什么，
see like the the
看到像
across the network to do that in spring
跨网络在春季做到这一点
you have something called spring class
你有所谓的春季班
ooh right right and we can actually use
对对对，我们可以实际使用
spring class food and store the trace
春季班食品并保存痕迹
data on Google cloud so you don't
数据存储在Google云上，因此您不必
necessarily have to run and manage your
一定要运行和管理您的
own Zipkin instances to see these traces
拥有Zipkin实例以查看这些痕迹
right right so so we can do that in
对对，所以我们可以在
addition to that we have logging
除此之外，我们还有日志记录
centralized loggers so over your log
集中式记录器，因此您的日志
thing I actually go into a centralized
我实际上进入一个集中的东西
place in Google cloud as well in the
放在Google云端
beautiful things is that we can actually
美丽的事情是，我们实际上可以
correlate you allowed messages with the
将您允许的消息与
trace data as well so do you wanna give
跟踪数据，所以你想给
this a try I don't know if you have a
这个尝试，我不知道你是否有一个
lot of time but huh you can do it all
很多时间，但是你可以做的所有
right so let's try it so I'm going to
对，让我们尝试一下，我将
say hello controllers so I'm going to
说你好控制器，所以我要
just make a quick controller here and
只是在这里做一个快速控制器
this is a rest controller of course and
这当然是一个 rest controller
I'm going to say public string like
我要说像
hello or something like that
你好或类似的东西
hello I can't get used to a keyboard
你好我不能习惯键盘
it's really hard to use you know so when
真的很难用你知道，所以当
I say hello plus the name right so I
我问好加上名字好，所以我
can't do that in fact how did you do
其实你做不到
that magical log4j thing okay that's
那个神奇的log4j事情还可以
pretty good so I'm going to logged on
很好，所以我要登录
info and name is whatever race I'm going
信息和名称是我要参加的比赛
to login the name and we also need to
登录名称，我们还需要
get the rest template in here so I can
在这里获取其余模板，这样我就可以
make the call
打电话
how did you do that one so I'm gonna say
你是怎么做到的，我要说
private final rice template yeah rice
私人最终大米模板是的大米
template okay and then the magical thing
模板好，然后神奇的事情
that you got here required arts
你来这里需要艺术
constructor from that is pretty awesome
那个的构造函数很棒
I like it and I need to get the rest and
我喜欢它，我需要休息一下，
play out somewhere so I'm gonna go back
在某个地方玩，我要回去
here I'm gonna say now why didn't you
在这里我要说的是为什么你不
just create the bean in line right then
只需在行中创建bean然后
and there because if you created the
在那里，因为如果您创建了
being then our interceptor is not going
然后我们的拦截器就不会
to be able to inject the stuff into the
能够将东西注入
rest and play so you've got
休息和玩耍，所以你有
configuration that looks for a spring
寻找Spring 的配置
bean definition in the application
应用程序中的bean定义
context of progress template and Kies is
进度模板和Kies的上下文是
it that's right so you have to do Claire
没错，所以您必须要做克莱尔
does it bean oh that's right yeah and
bean  bean 吗，是的，是的，
what happens in this will do the trace
这会发生什么将跟踪
ID propagation for you automatically so
自动为您传播ID
when you stress template to make a call
当您强调模板打电话时
well automatically add the trace IDs to
以及自动将跟踪ID添加到
the header as well and that's out of the
标头也是如此
box functionality from lumber from
木材的包装箱功能从
springhouse cool that's right so the one
斯普林豪斯很酷，这是对的
thing that we changed is the where the
我们改变的是
trace actually go ok and then let's just
跟踪实际上可以，然后让我们
make another in point here so this is a
在这里提出另一个要点，所以这是一个
get right
正确
so get mapping I'm gonna say this is
所以获取地图，我要说的是
hello in a nice to you another one here
你好，对你好
I'm gonna go Floyd and I'm gonna say oh
我要去弗洛伊德，我要说哦
ok and what this one will do is to just
好，这个人要做的就是
make a few calls to hello right so we
打电话打个招呼吧，所以我们
can see that the trace happening so what
可以看到跟踪正在发生
did you do this year before and let's
你今年前做过，让我们
string off I'm gonna say Josh we can get
我要说乔什我们可以得到
the repository right you know we could
您知道我们可以的存储库权利
also but let's just try this one out
还可以，让我们尝试一下
giochi shout is one of the co-workers of
giochi shout是以下组织的同事之一
mine who wrote a lot of the spring
我的春天写的很多
cloudy sepia as well anyone else and you
乌贼墨乌云密布的人，还有你
want to say hi to Jim Jim James yeah so
想对吉姆·吉姆·詹姆斯打个招呼，是的，所以
here we can have the name and then for
在这里我们可以有一个名字，然后
each other name we're going to do it
彼此的名字，我们要去做
rest and play we're going to get four
休息和玩，我们将获得四个
entity for example the URL which is
实体，例如网址为
localhost 8080 hello
本地主机8080你好
right and name is equal to the name that
权利和名称等于
we passing right and this is going to be
我们通过正确的，这将是
a string class string class because I
字符串类，因为我
don't really care about my response okay
真的不在乎我的反应好吗
yep now to add the trace into it this is
是的，现在添加跟踪到它是
what you do you go to the pump and of
你要去的泵和
course we have stronger for it so what
当然我们对此有更强的实力
is happening there yeah so I'm gonna go
是在那里发生，所以我要去
ahead and add the trace starter so here
前面并添加跟踪启动器，所以在这里
we have GCP starter trace okay and that
我们有GCP入门跟踪文件，而且
should be it
应该是
oh by the way we sprinkle by default
哦，顺便说一句，我们默认洒
only trace 10% of the request so we're
仅跟踪请求的10％，所以我们
going to update to 100% so we can see
将更新到100％，这样我们就可以看到
everything right and it's it's only 10%
一切都很好，只有10％
because you don't need more than that to
因为您只需要
see the big picture usually but for our
通常看大图，但对于我们
demo we're not gonna I'm not gonna do 10
演示，我们不会，我不会做10
requests just so you can see one of them
请求只是为了您可以看到其中之一
oh we're just do one so you can see one
哦，我们只是做一个，所以你可以看到一个
right yeah so let's see if this works
是的，让我们看看是否可行
I'm going to restart this again I'm
我要重新启动一次
going to make a few calls and then we're
要打几个电话，然后我们
going to be able to see hopefully the
希望能够看到
traces that I can with this as well okay
我也可以做到的痕迹
Oh your message you still here
哦，你的留言你还在这里
oh that's because you're always sending
哦，那是因为你一直在发送
the hollow message all the time right
总是无聊的消息
yeah and we see the resource okay let's
是的，我们看到资源好了，让我们
give it a try so here we have the test
试试看，所以这里有测试
HTTP I'm going to go ahead and do get
HTTP我将继续进行并获得
HTTP localhost 8080 /o and I'm sweating
HTTP localhost 8080 / o，我出汗了
here because I'm not quite sure
在这里，因为我不太确定
is going to work well it kind of did
会做得很好
okay if I go back to the run here we can
好吧，如果我回到这里跑步，我们可以
see actually made a call so we got Josh
看到实际上打了电话，所以我们得到了乔希
Reitan James well as you can see here is
里坦·詹姆斯（Reitan James）很好，您可以看到这里是
that very clearly we have the trace ID
很明显，我们有跟踪ID
that's being propagated across the call
正在整个通话中传播
and the trace ID is the same across the
并且跟踪ID在整个
coast stack and then we got each of the
海岸栈，然后我们得到了每个
coats as different span but we also
外套的跨度不同，但我们也
added the trace daughter so what that's
添加了追踪女儿，那是什么
supposed to do also is that if we go
应该做的是，如果我们去
back to Google Cloud console if we go to
回到Google Cloud控制台
the trace feature here I'm sweating here
我在这里流汗的跟踪功能
if I go to the trace list yes we we kind
如果我去跟踪列表，是的，我们友善
of got this right if we if this actually
如果我们真的有这个权利，
worked
工作了
oh there this so it does say local host
哦，所以这确实说本地主机
dress now so let me see if I can click
现在穿衣服，让我看看是否可以点击
into it oh oh not bad yeah usually the
哦，哦，还不错，通常
trace will show up in the dot but for
跟踪将显示在点中，但对于
some reason it's not seen yet but here
由于某种原因，它尚未出现，但在这里
we can very clearly see the entire Coast
我们可以很清楚地看到整个海岸
tag just like that by adding a simple
像这样通过添加一个简单的标签
starter to your application without
入门到您的应用程序而无需
adding any other configuration - awesome
添加任何其他配置-很棒
yeah pretty nice right that's hot sauce
是的，很好，很辣
man
男人
yeah pounded yam Mike awesome okay so
是的，捣烂山药Mike很棒，所以
what do we do we saw how if use spring
我们该怎么办，我们看到如果使用Spring
and spring cloud and spring boot to
和春天的云和春天引导到
build applications that run Abele on
构建在其上运行Abele的应用程序
infrastructure like Google cloud
Google Cloud等基础架构
naturally it is my every hope that
我自然希望
you're gonna use something like cloud
你会用像云一样的东西
foundry or PKS pivotal kubernetes
铸造或PKS关键kubernetes
pivotal container servers or something
关键的容器服务器之类的
on top of Google Cloud but then once
在Google Cloud之上，但随后一次
there your apps are going to need to
您的应用将需要
talk to interesting infrastructure we've
与我们有趣的基础设施进行对话
looked at how to build how to talk to
看着如何建立如何与之交谈
data stores how to talk to span or
数据存储如何交谈跨度或
distributed distributed multi regional
分布式分布式多区域
data store that has transactions we
有交易的数据存储
looked at how to build applications that
研究了如何构建应用程序
do pub/sub we looked at how to do build
做pub / sub，我们研究了如何做
applications that do storage we can you
我们可以做存储的应用程序
actually use the storage and talk to the
实际使用存储并与
storage API we also looked at how to do
存储API我们还研究了如何做
crazy mind-bending futuristic like you
像你这样疯狂的思维弯曲未来派
know the the singularity kind of stuff
知道奇点的东西
for machine learning and image detection
用于机器学习和图像检测
and then finally to operationalize that
然后最终实现
we looked at Google clouds straight race
我们看了看Google云端直赛
yeah support we so that was fun that was
是的，支持我们，所以那很有趣
pretty awesome right yeah thank you
太棒了，是的，谢谢
everybody
大家
we learned something new who learned
我们学到了一些新的知识
something new today good stuff yeah yeah
今天有新东西不错，是的
check out the project give it a try and
签出该项目尝试一下
yeah absolutely wonderful Thanks and I
是的，绝对很棒，谢谢，我
think I'm doing a book signing and they
以为我在做书签，他们
say at least I think I am if not either
说至少我想我也是
way it should be coming to the pivotal
它应该成为关键的方式
booth I'm pretty sure I'm doing a book
摊位，我很确定我正在读书
signing come there or I think he'll be
签到那里，否则我想他会
here well he'll be with me there and
在这里，他会和我在一起，
we'll answer questions and exactly do
我们会回答问题并完全做到
all that stuff yeah Cheers
所有这些东西，是的，干杯
thank you so much boys
非常感谢男孩们
[Music]
[音乐]